Adam Zdrzałka



PHONE 786 266 604 EMAIL adam.2drz@gmail.com

Profile

Ambitious software developer with a large technological stack which results from my passion for technology. Over two yeas of experience, mostly in Web Technologies. I am always willing to share my experiences for example from my winning the biggest hackathon in the world episodes.

Education

Oct 2017 - Present

WROCŁAW

University of Economics

IT in business.

Oct 2016 - Jun 2017

WROCŁAW

University of Science and Technology

After a year of full-time study I've stopped them to completely focus on work and start part-

time study.

Sep 2012 - Apr 2016

OŁAWA

Zespół Szkół Ponadgimnazjalnych nr 2

IT specialist

Languages

English



Certificates and achievements

Nov 2018 – Nov 2018

WARSAW

Member of winning team in two categories on hackathon HackYeah 2018

Member of winning in two categories on HackYeah 2018. Where in 24h, me and my team created Loyalty application for Orlen based on blockchain and application which was the best in opinion Ministry of Health, to solve the issue which their called "Health need maps"

Skills

Java MySQL Angular 6 PostgreSQL
NoSQL
JavaScript

HTML	••••	CSS/SCSS	••••
Hibernate	••••	Flyway	••••
JDBC	••••	SOLID	••••
Jenkins	••••	Elasticsearch	••••
Docker	••••	RESTful API	••••
Spring	••••	Linux	••••
ActiveMQ	• • • • •	AngularJS	••••

Employment History

Apr 2017 - Mar 2019 WROCŁAW

Full-stack Java Developer

SerwisPrawa.pl sp. z o.o.

- Creating RESTful Web Services in Spring applications.
- Creating SQL queries to retrieve data from the database also using JDBC.
- · Working with orm framework like hibernate and as a migration tool flyway.
- Developing Web applications on multiple platforms.
- Estimated work hours and tracked progress using Agile/SCRUM methodology.
- Code review for members of team.
- Preparing environment with docker container and managing them.
- Working with continuous integration systems like Jenkins and Drone.
- Working with existing software to correct errors, upgrade interfaces and improve performance.
- Creating unit tests in JUnit also a bit with Mockito .
- Integration with backend side services using Angular also creating views with HTML, CSS/SCSS and NativeScript components.

Mar 2019 - Present WROCŁAW

Full-stack Java Developer

KRUK S.A.

- Design architecture of the web application(frontend and backend).
- Working with orm framework like hibernate and as a migration tool Liquibase.
- Taking a part of refinement process to find best solutions and implement them.
- Develop big process web application based on ActiveMQ.
- Develop smaller web applications based on microservices,
- Estimated work hours and tracked progress using Agile/SCRUM methodology.
- Reviewing code.
- Preparing continuous integration process for web applications using Jenkins, Docker.
- Covering code with Unit tests.
- Integration with backend side services using Angular
- $\bullet \ \ {\it Creating templates with HTML, CSS/SCSS, Bootstrap}.$
- Creating RESTful Web Services in Spring applications.